Do you see that? Ooh. Oh ****
**** **** **** I was looking at
the wrong building. Alright,
there's three of em over here.
Enemy movement. About to joker
the **** out of him. There's
multiple groups there too. This
is perfect timing. Okay.
Team. Get the hell going. Get
the hell going.
I just killed three of them
with this helicopter.
Yep, I got, I knocked him.
Although he just put a trophy
system out in front. I down
him. I'm inside. Down one. Got
another. Oh god damn it.
I got.
Team wiped him.
I downed him. **** Somebody
inside but
Uh crossbow. See ya.
Hostile dropping into the area.
Watch the skies.
Oh.
Dropping into the area. Watch
the skies. Head.
Nasty yo.
I got him. One shot at him.